<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeremy Elkayam</title>
    <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeremy Elkayam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go To The Toilet</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/projects/gotoilet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/projects/gotoilet/</guid>
      <description>Go To The Toilet is an animated music video for the song Go To The Toilet by Dave Bulmer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t make the song, but everything you see in the video was drawn and animated by me. I worked on this video during my free time at university from April 2019 to March 2020. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t at school over the summer of 2019 (mid-May to mid-August), so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t working on it then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Crazy Weekend</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/show-and-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 15:37:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/show-and-trip/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve had a very busy past few days. Everything about my weekend has had to do with the sketch comedy group that I&amp;rsquo;m a part of here at college, called 7th Grade Sketch Comedy. Sometime soon I&amp;rsquo;ll do a deeper dive into why exactly I&amp;rsquo;ve put so much of myself into sketch comedy over the past 3 1/2 years of school, but for now it&amp;rsquo;s important to know that I collaborate on sketch shows with these people and we also make videos together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Website</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/first-post-on-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 17:19:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/first-post-on-website/</guid>
      <description>Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jeremy Elkayam. I made a website because I figured it was time I had one. It has a blog, because I wanted it to have a blog. I like to write about things that I do, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to do that on this blog.
Where I Started Because I like to do things out of order, the first thing I did was register a domain name. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to do that first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a 22-year-old computer geek with a lot of different interests. I&amp;rsquo;ve taken to labeling myself as a &amp;ldquo;thing maker&amp;rdquo; because, while extremely broad, it&amp;rsquo;s a nice catch-all for the things in my life that I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about. I have a BS in computer science and I get paid to develop software, but I also make apps and games on my own time for no reason other than personal fulfillment. I&amp;rsquo;ve dabbled in almost every medium of digital art for one project or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Fight</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/projects/tower-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 18:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/projects/tower-defense/</guid>
      <description>Food Fight was a 2D tower-defense video game created for the class Intro to Video Game Design and Development at William &amp;amp; Mary. The game features a 4 different tower types with branching upgrades for a total of 16 towers, 3 different types of enemies with procedural variation in stats, a money system, and procedurally generated maps. All of the game&amp;rsquo;s artwork was created by me. I also did a lot of programming work on the project, creating all of the enemy unit systems, and helping to debug the map creation engine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>