<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jeremy Elkayam</title>
    <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jeremy Elkayam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 15:47:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Animal Crossing to Discover My Taste</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/anti-mimesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 15:47:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/anti-mimesis/</guid>
      <description>Just like most people who can afford video games, I’ve spent the last few months playing Animal Crossing: New Horizons, the latest entry in Nintendo’s long-running Animal Crossing franchise. I’ve been playing Animal Crossing since I was eight years old, but I’ve been playing this one a bit differently from how I’ve played in the past. Now, for the first time ever, my choices in dressing up my Animal Crossing character have begun to define how I dress in real life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Crazy Weekend</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/show-and-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 15:37:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/show-and-trip/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve had a very busy past few days. Everything about my weekend has had to do with the sketch comedy group that I&amp;rsquo;m a part of here at college, called 7th Grade Sketch Comedy. Sometime soon I&amp;rsquo;ll do a deeper dive into why exactly I&amp;rsquo;ve put so much of myself into sketch comedy over the past 3 1/2 years of school, but for now it&amp;rsquo;s important to know that I collaborate on sketch shows with these people and we also make videos together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Website</title>
      <link>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/first-post-on-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 17:19:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jeremyelkayam.com/posts/first-post-on-website/</guid>
      <description>Hi, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Jeremy Elkayam. I made a website because I figured it was time I had one. It has a blog, because I wanted it to have a blog. I like to write about things that I do, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to do that on this blog.
Where I Started Because I like to do things out of order, the first thing I did was register a domain name. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to do that first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>